MICHAEL PIETROSKI

mpworkplace@gmail.com

9736527269

linkedin.com/in/michaelpietroski

https://vppelli.github.io/portfolio-website/

Summary

I have a strong background in Art, having completed 2 years of courses in Architecture at Essex County College and received an Advanced 3D Modeling Diploma from CG Spectrum College of Digital Art and Animation. Worked as a 3D Environment Artist at Soul Les Games and Metabuff, where I created realistic and stylized environment assets, props to creatures, and full game environments.

With multiple certifications in 3D modeling this helped build up many skills, being proficient in PBR textures, UV tiling, and optimizing game ready assets.

I am an avid video game player and a passionate 3D Artist, who is always striving to push my career forward and bring out the best in my teammates, friends, co-workers, and myself.

Using software like Unreal Engine 4 & 5, Maya, Adobe & Substance Products, ZBrush and CAD software's too. Great at Realistic art, Stylized art, being agile, flexible, bilingual, and eager to learn new skills and technologies. Looking for a company that inspires creativity in there Artists.

Experience



3D Modeler

Kitesurf Technologies

Oct 2022 - Present (1 year 4 months)

- 3D Rendering ready Assets
- · High-quality textures, Uv Tiling, and Optimizing game ready assets
- Modeling and creating assets for in-game Simulator
- · Liaising with Lead, Engineers and other Artists

3D Environment Artist

Soul Les Games LLC

Dec 2021 - Jan 2023 (1 year 2 months)

- 3D Modeling and creating Tiled textures, Trim sheets and Multi Gradient texture in Substance Designer and Substance Painter.
- High-quality artwork stylized Environment Assets
- Create environments, villages, and dungeons
- Liaising with the Art Director, Lead Artist and other Artists
- Working with Unreal Engine 4 & 5, Maya, Substance Designer, Substance Painter, and Photoshop



3D Environment Artist

Metabuff

May 2018 - Jul 2019 (1 year 3 months)

- 3D Modeling and creating PBR Textures using Maya and Substance painter
- · High-quality artwork, wide range of realistic and stylized Environment Assets
- Create full 3D Environments, ensuring artwork follows project style and standards
- Liaising with the Art Director, Lead Artist and other Artists

• Worked with Unreal Engine 4, Maya, ZBrush, and Substance Painter

Education

CF CareerFoundry

Full Stack, Web Developer 2023 - Present

CG Spectrum

Advanced 3D Modeling, Art/Art Studies, General 2020 - 2022

Essex County College

Associate, Arts; Architecture 2018 - 2020

Licenses & Certifications

Advanced 3D Modeling Certificate - CG Spectrum 749834

Skills

Unreal Engine • Texture Mapping • 3D Modeling • Digital Sculpting • UV Mapping • ZBrush • Substance Painter • Autodesk Maya • Lighting • Substance Designer